Guide to the Harris Masterson I papers,1860-1942, bulk 1880-1920 MS 468
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series VII: Personal files (Box 263)
  - Prewitt, John M. (Box 263, Folder 32)
  - Prince Ranch (Box 263, Folder 33)
  - Rice Institute (Box 263, Folder 34)
  - Sawyer, F.A. (Box 263, Folder 35)
  - Sharp, W.H. (Box 263, Folder 36)
  - Smith, C.D. (Box 263, Folder 37)
  - South Dakota - Texas Oil Co. (Box 263, Folder 38)
  - Stewart, John McNeill (Box 263, Folder 39)
  - Stringfellow and Menard (Box 263, Folder 40)
  - Texas (early) (Box 263, Folder 41)
  - Texas documents (early) (Box 263, Folder 42)
  - Texas documents, Brazoria County (early) (Box 263, Folder 43)
  - Viesca Survey (Box 263, Folder 44)
- Series VIII: Ledgers (Boxes 264-278)
  - Ledger: Expenses and cash, 1908-1920; Ledger: Accounts, 1939-1940 (Box 264)
  - Dockets, 1904-1908; Accounts book, 1921-1937; Harris County District Court Records for Masterson, 1910s; Land and tax records, ca. 1900-1919 (Box 265)
  - Accounts books (2), 1920s-1940s; Commissioner's report of Townsite property divided, Ross Masterson's land interest shown in this book, 1905; Cash Book, 1909-1912 (Box 266)
  - La Jarza Oil Company Directors Minute Book, Houston, TX, 1904-1910;Cash Book II for T.T.L. I. Co., 1911; Powell Lumber Co. paid invoices, 1910; Cash book, 1904-1906; Lone Star Bag Bagging Co. / Long Reach Bagging Southern Bagging Co. / International Cottonseed Products Directory, 1935-36 (Box 267)
  - Journal: Clivesburg, TX, 1902; Journal: Nov. 1903-Dec. 1906 (Box 268)
  - Bills discounted register, 1910; Accounts journal, 1904-1908; Ledger: Texas Town Lot Improvement Co., 1906-1914 (Box 269)
  - Account book, 1896-1905; Masterson Irrigation Co. note register, 1909-1914; Journal: Texas Town Lot Improvement Co., 1906-1921 (Box 270)
  - Land register, 1899-1908; Accounts recapitulation ledger, 1910; Rent ledger, 1917; Land accounts ledger (index?), n.d. (Box 271)
  - Personal account book, 1905; Note register, 1918-1919 (Box 272)
  - Business and personal ledger, 1903-1906; Cash book, 1912-1915 (Box 273)
  - Land abstracts journal, 1881-1913; D.E. ledger, journal, 1919-19127; Winfree-Biggs Contracting Co. stock certificate book, 1919 (Box 274)
  - Account ledger, 1904-1908; Land ledger (index?), n.d.; Note register, 1913; Shelp Rubber Supply Co. / Texas Rubber Supply Co. minute book, 1909-1910; Account book, 1897-1899 (Box 275)
  - Ledger: Houston Town Lot Improvement Co. 1902-1903; Ledger: Masterson Rogers 1903 (2); Land sales account book, 1902-1906 (Box 276)
  - Accounts ledger, 1900-1901; Masterson Rogers accounts ledger, 1903; Rent ledger, 1907-1910; Daybook, ----Oil Co., 1901 (Box 277)
  - Ledger: Brazoria Co., 1896-1902; Land abstracts for Live Oak Co., TX, 1860s-1880s; Central Bank Trust Co. cash book, 1907-1909 (Box 278)
- Series IX: Oversize materials (Boxes 279-282)
  Related Materials
  Oversize materials are also located in map drawers. See https://txarchives.org/ricewrc/finding_aids/00761.xml for more information.
  Missing Items - Box 281
  --Houston city taxes for H. Masterson., 3-16-1905. --Letter from J. Sunsheime to H. Masterson and the account of the audit by Mr. Hart in the Mims-Hardy matter., 7-3-1916. --Record of accounts for 1892. (4 pages). --Quit-claim deed for land in Brazoria, TX. Edwin C. Estes Mary A.T. Lord., 10-15-1874. --Condition of titles in the A.G. Reynolds League, Brazoria Co., TX. --Bill of sale of land in Nacogdoches Co., The Republic of Texas by Candido Sanches to Roberts Allen Phillips., 5-13-1837. --Certificate of ownership by J.L. Hudson of 4 shares of stock in the International Oil Mineral Company., 6-24-1898. --Twenty shares of $100 each of capital stock of J.L. Hudson Patent Company of Houston, TX. 8-4-1898. --Inventory of appraisement of property owned by Texas Town Lot Improvement Company in the city of Houston., 1-1-1911. --Notice of public sale of land in Brazoria Co., 6-25-1856. --Insurance policy for the Farmer's Union of Coleman Co. (Niagara Insurance Co.)., 10-4-1907. --Family tree for Elizabeth Glass McGalen lineage. --Insurance policy for Mrs. N.H. Bailey, Crowley, LA., 2-17-1906. --Insurance policy for Mrs. L.A. Ellis, administratrix of the estate of L.A. Ellis-deceased., 12-18-1905. --Insurance policy for Mrs. L.A. Ellis., 3-24-1905. --Insurance policy for Mrs. J.V. Westmoreland., 1-3-1907 to 1-3-1908. --Insurance policy for J.R. McGoven., 3-16-1906 to 3-16-1907. --Insurance policy for A.S. Lacy., 9-4-1895 to 9-4-1896 --Insurance policy for J.H. Ratcliff, trustee Toomey Lumber Co., Ltd., 3-11-1905 to 3-11-1906. --Declaration of bankruptcy by R.H. Downey., 1-7-1902. --Inventory of appraisement of property owned by H. Masterson in the city of Houston., 1-1-1903. --Insurance policy to William Jefferson Powell., 5-28-1909. --Insurance policy to Clara S. Masterson, wife of Thomas G. Masterson., 2-25-1892. --Insurance policy to Mrs. L.A. Ellis, administratrix for the estate of L.A. Ellis, deceased., 4-10-1905 to 4-10-1906. --Refunding certificate for money heretofore paid for paring- for Mrs. Minnie Sterne, Houston, TX., 12-20-1900. --(8) First mortgage bonds for $500 from the Riverside Coal Investment Co., Des Moines, Iowa., 8-1-1889. --Document establishing the corporation of the South Dakota-Texas Oil Company., 5-16-1908. --Insurance policy for the Farmer's Union of Coleman County., 10-4-1906 to 10-4-1907. --Sale of the estate of E.B. Lynch-deceased- by W.C.C. Lynch, administrator to Winthrop D. Cushman., 6-11-1856. --Piece of paper with listings for H. Masterson, Lovejoy, Gill, Jas. Biste, R.A. Welch, Sinclair. --Insurance policy for R.N. Downey., 6-12-1900 to 6-12-1901. --Insurance policy for Mrs. L.A. Ellis. 3-24-1905 to 3-24-1906 (Aetna Co.). --Insurance policy for Mrs. L.A. Ellis. 3-24-1905 to 3-24-1906 (Springfield Fire Marine Insurance Co.). --Insurance policy for Mrs. L.A. Ellis. 4-18-1905 to 4-14-1906 (Virginia Fire Marine Insurance Co.). --Insurance policy for Mrs. L.A. Ellis. 6-14-1905 to 6-14-1906 (Providence Washington Insurance Co.). --Insurance policy for A.W. Paliner W. Abmy (Houston Book Co.). 12-11-1905 to 12-11-1906 (Standard Mutual Fire Insurance Co.). --Insurance policy for Mrs. J.V. Westmoreland., 10-16-1906 to 10-16-1907. --Siegfred Gruner Sub. Division showing sales of Robertson Co. and sales of Leon Co.
  Missing Items - Box 282
  --Insurance policy for H. Masterson., 6-12-1901 to 6-12-1902 --Receipts for 1902. --Insurance policy for the Farmer's Union Warehouse Assoc. of Coleman Co., 10-4-1906 to 10-4-1907. --List description of lands (11 pages). --Time roll of labor performed by employees of Houston Transfer Carriage Co. for the month of November, (7 pages)., 1909 --Land grant to Samuel C. Lyons from the Republic of Texas- 8 1/3 labors of land in Jackson Co., Anson Jones-President., 8-8-1845. --List and description of land sold from 7-24-1912 to 2-10-1913. --List and description of land sold from 4-12-1902 to 7-20-1912. --Transfers beginning with #32 ending with #36, since 6-18-1890 to 6-9-1891, as shown by the Harris Co. records (8 pages). --Indebtedness contested by Allen to J. Sweeney. 8-3-1905 to 2-5-1908 (5 pages). --Land grant dated Feb. 18, 1863. --Insurance policy for Mrs. J.V. Westmoreland (The Liverpool and London and Globe Insurance Company- policy #125210). Dated, Jan. 3, 1907. --First of purchasers dated from 4-12-1909 to 7-20-1912. --"Sold To" list (ca. 7-24-1912). --(2) Inventories of appraisement for H. Masterson. Dated, June 1, 1919.
  - Sketch of part of Brazoria County, General Land Office (has #153 on back), September 22, 1886 (Box 279, Item 1)
  - Earnest receipt received by H. Masterson 500.00 as part payment for two tracts, one containing 4 acres and the other 28.28 acres. (Box 279, Item 2)
  - Ira P. Jones to J.O. Ross [copy], May 7, 1915; Ross to Judge A. Masterson, Sept. 22, 1915; Ross to Masterson, Oct. 10, 1915, concerning a boundary dispute). Map located in Drawer 72. (Box 279, Item 3)
  - Letter dated Aug. 5, 1896 from H.H. MacNicoll to H. Masterson relative to land dispute. Map located in Drawer 72. (Box 279, Item 4)
  - Plat of section no. 6, H.T. B.R.R. Co. Surveyed Oct. 11-13, 1894 R.W. Priest, Surveyor. (Box 279, Item 5)
  - Sketch of subdivision along Mound Creek-San Bernard River with "Zeno Phillips" on corner. (Box 279, Item 6)
  - Maps of Gothland. Property of M.A., J.H., and W.W. Hoskins. Field Notes of "Caldwell tract." (Box 279, Item 7)
  - Sketch of Wisdom 1/2 league and letter to Judge Masterson, July 2, 1917 (Box 279, Item 8)
  - Section no. 23, Hooper Wade survey, Brazoria Co., TX. On reverse affidavit dated January 4, 1900. Also affidavit signed by H. Masterson, November 1890 (in 2 pieces). (Box 279, Item 9)
  - Letter dated January 8, 1909, from Gaines Corbett, lawyers of Bay City, to Mr. Harry Masterson concerning a land dispute; (2) a summons to South Texas Development Co. H. Masterson, to appear in Brazoria Co. Court on a suit over the matter dated January 26, 1909; (3) a copy of the petition for suit, with county clerk's endorsement. Plat located in Map Drawer 72. (Box 279, Item 10)
  - Plat of the J.E.A. Phelps league, H. Stevens, C.S.B.C. (marked as #112)., February 1876. (Box 279, Item 11)
  - Notarized earnest receipt, signed E.L.R. Wheelock, witnessed by Ben W. Chilton, notary public, Jefferson Co., TX, Nov. 13, 1903 (very fragile, marked as #21). (Box 279, Item 12)
  - Map of the Sanderson tract in Andrew Robinson league, Brazoria Co., TX. (Box 279, Item 13)
  - Warehouse no. 2, Farmers and Bankers Warehouse Building Assoc. (1) Building contract, (2) Cotton warehouse no. 2 equipment list, (3) Exhibit "B"- standard specifications. (Box 279, Item 14)
  - Cotton warehouse no. 1, Farmers Union Warehouse Co., of Wewaka, Thirteenth District, Indian Territory. (1)Building contract, (2) Exhibit "A" - description of property, (3) Exhibit "B" - cotton warehouse no. 1 equipment list, (4) Exhibit "B"- standard specifications. (Box 279, Item 15)
  - Map of Davis and J.R. Shannon's land in Brazoria, TX., [189?] (Box 279, Item 16)
  - Letter from Mimmi Co. Trimble to Mr. J.R. Masterson, from Montgomery, AL., June 22, 1909. (Box 279, Item 17)
  - Letter from J.F. Stimmer, Gonzales State Bank and Trust Co., Gonzales, TX, to Elliott Cage, Attorney at Law, Houston, TX., August 13, 1917. (Box 279, Item 18)
  - Map of Houston and an approximate 5 mile radius. (Box 279, Item 19)
  - Partition of Mimms Estate (Box 279, Item 20)
  - Map showing the division of lots between Milam and Marrell streets, executed by H. Masterson, Attorney at Law, Brazoria, TX., [188?] (Box 279, Item 21)
  - Map showing abstract 463, section 24, F (Box 279, Item 22)
  - Map showing abstract 569-A.A. Ballard (640 acres, Homer (320 acres), H. Masterson (160 acres), and B.J. Masterson (160 acres)). (Box 279, Item 23)
  - Plot of Henry Austin league #6. (Box 279, Item 24)
  - Map of "Saved in Travis Co.", showing the Elenor Mudd Plot, the Pease Plot, and two other plots. (Box 279, Item 25)
  - Map of the correction of the river boundary line of the A. Calvit league, Robert B. Harris Co. (Box 279, Item 26)
  - Sketch/Blueprint of Battle, Berry and Williams league, Matagorda Co., October 12-13, 1923. (Box 279, Item 27)
  - Subdivision of acre lot 12 from the Heart tract out of the S. Jackson league, Hardin Co., TX, blueprint. (Box 279, Item 28)
  - Map of the Saratoga Oil Field. Blueprint. (Box 279, Item 29)
  - Survey of the McGowan addition. Blueprint. (Box 279, Item 30)
  - Survey of part of a 357.75 acre tract in J.P. Cockrell Survey, Harris and Fort Bend Co. Blueprint., February 10, 1919. (Box 279, Item 31)
  - Plat of 11-1/2 acres, J.T. Boyles Minors, Wilson and Harris, 2 leagues, located 1-3/4 miles from the Houston city limits on Buffalo Bayou. Blueprint., August 1908. (Box 279, Item 32)
  - Matagorda County Abstract Company. Note from Robert H. Traylor and sketch of Matagorda Pasture., June 9, 1900. (Box 279, Item 33)
  - Map showing Acres of William Clark League. (Very fragile) (Box 279, Item 34)
  - Letter to Gen. Sam Houston, July 26, 1836 from Henry Swartz, Richwood Union County Ohio. (Box 279, Item 35)
  - Amount of Claims allowed and drafts drawn but unpaid. (Box 279, Item 36)
  - Abstract of rejected vouchers, for expenditures in first and second quarter of 1840 for disbursements by William S. Gazneau, Commissary Gen. Subsistence. (Box 279, Item 37)
  - Land sale, county of Nacogdoches, from Candido Sanchez, May 13, 1837. (Box 279, Item 38)
  - Texas Scrip 640 Acres of Land John G. Budd, September 26, 1836. (Box 279, Item 39)
  - Etching "The first recorded surgical operation in North America: Cabeza de Vaca-Taking the arrowhead from the Indian's chest, in West Texas in the year 1535." Tom Lea, 1965. (Box 279, Item 40)
  - Sketch showing the Southeastern Portion of Pecos County, Texas and letter from Oliver L. Ellis attached., March 28, 1886. (Box 279, Item 41)
  - Special Bargain List of Lands for Sale, Beaumont, Texas. (Box 279, Item 42)
  - Map of New Birmingham, Cherokee County, Texas. (Box 279, Item 43)
  - Map of Robertson County, 1952. Copy. (Box 279, Item 44)
  - Sketch of G. W. Robinson 1509 acres. (Box 279, Item 45)
  - Special Circular to purchasers of our health-pamphlet. A Wilford Hall, New York. (Box 279, Item 46)
  - Interesting facts about Mineral Developments in Llano County, Texas. (Box 279, Item 47)
  - West Mountain School for Males and Females Announcement for 1884. (Box 279, Item 48)
  - 8 black white photographs of J. Frank Dobie. (Box 279, Item 49)
  - Family Tree of Mos. McGalan Elizabeth Glass McGalan. (Box 280, Item 1)
  - (6) pages written in Chinese (very fragile). (Box 280, Item 2)
  - (2) Poll tax receipts-1909 for Precinct 16- Cedar Bayou. (Box 280, Item 3)
  - Part of a constitution for a corporation (practice writing in Chinese on back) (Box 280, Item 4)
  - Practice sheet of Chinese writing (Box 280, Item 5)
  - (3) Poll tax receipts-1909 for Harris Co. (notes on "Diagonal High Pressure" on back). In two parts. (Box 280, Item 6)
  - (2) Income tax forms for 191[?] (Box 280, Item 7)
  - Certificate of redemption to H. Masterson, Chronicle Bldg., Houston, TX., 1-31-1921 (Box 280, Item 8)
  - Certificate of redemption to Masterson Irrigation Co., 7-6-1912. (Box 280, Item 9)
  - Certificate of redemption to F. Hunt., 9-29-1898. (Box 280, Item 10)
  - Insurance - misc. (Box 280, Item 11)
  - Certificate of redemption to Masterson Irrigation Co., 1-29-1915. (Box 280, Item 12)
  - Tax Assessments - misc. (Box 280, Item 13)
  - Debts, Sales - misc. (Box 280, Item 14)
  - Land grant to Samuel Everett, 640 acres, Harris County. Commissioned by Governor F. R. Lubbock., 2-18-1863. (Box 280, Item 15)
  - (4) Certificates for five shares in Phoenix Lumber Company to J. L. Heedson., 3-19-1897. (Box 280, Item 16)
  - (21) Certificates of sale of land by Hitchcock City Land. Joint stock assoc. to Charles L. Cleveland. Nos.- 123, 122, 120, 115, 112, 101, 100, 96, 95, 94, 91, 88, 85, 84, 83, 78, 77, 74, 72, 70, 69., 7-1-1890. (Box 280, Item 17)
  - Tax form for the city of Houston to H. Masterson., 12-28-1905. (Box 280, Item 18)
  - Inventory of appraisement of property owned by Texas Town Lot Improvement Company in the city of Houston, TX. Taxes beginning 1-1-1917. (Box 280, Item 19)
  - Inventory of appraisement of property owned by Texas Town Lot Improvement Company in the city of Houston, TX. Taxes beginning 1-1-1911 (Box 280, Item 20)
  - Certificate of redemption to H. Masterson., 11-15-1915. (Box 280, Item 21)
  - Certificate of authentication to Cameron Co., 12-29-1915. (Box 280, Item 22)
  - Certificate of redemption to H. Masterson., 10-15-1913. (Box 280, Item 23)
  - Certificate of redemption- for land bid off to the State- to W .H. Haynes., 3-19-1900. (Box 280, Item 24)
  - Certificate of redemption to Bassett Blakely., 10-28-1918. (Box 280, Item 25)
  - (2) Redemption receipt to T.S. Masterson. 12-24-1923. (Box 280, Item 26)
  - Certificate of redemption to H. Masterson., 10-26-1917. (Box 280, Item 27)
  - Certificate of redemption to N.T. Masterson., 5-28-1921. (Box 280, Item 28)
  - Certificate of redemption for land sold for taxes to T.J. W.J. Moore., 11- 20-1900. (Box 280, Item 29)
  - (20) Inventories for appraisement for property owned by Texas Town Lot Improvement Company in the city of Houston., 1-1-1912. (Box 280, Item 30)
  - Letter from tax collector to Masterson Irrigation Company in Beaumont, TX., 3-20-1917. (Box 280, Item 31)
  - Statement of taxes done on land in Beaumont, TX to Masterson Irrigation Company., 3-23-1917. (Box 280, Item 32)
  - Letter from tax collector in Beaumont, TX to H. Masterson- threatening to sue over delinquent taxes., 4-18-1917. (Box 280, Item 33)
  - Inventory of property owned by Masterson Irrigation Company., 4-25-1917. (Box 280, Item 34)
  - Inventory of appraisement of property owned by Texas Town Lot Improvement Company in the city of Houston., 1-1-1907. (Box 280, Item 35)
  - Houston city taxes to Texas Town Lot Improvement Company., 12-21-1907. (Box 280, Item 36)
  - City tax receipt for 1907 to H. Masterson. (Box 280, Item 37)
  - Houston city taxes to Texas Town Lot Improvement Company., 12-28-1911. (Box 280, Item 38)
  - Inventory of appraisement of property owned by Texas Town Lot Improvement Company in the city of Houston. (2 pages)., 1-1-1911 (Box 280, Item 39)
  - Houston city taxes to Texas Town Lot Improvement Company., 12-23- 1908. (Box 280, Item 40)
  - Inventory of appraisement of property owned by Texas Town Lot Improvement Company in the city of Houston. (2 pages)., 1-1-190[?]. (Box 280, Item 41)
  - Houston city taxes to Texas Town Lot Improvement Company., 1910 (Box 280, Item 42)
  - Inventory of appraisement of property owned by Texas Town Lot Improvement Company in the city of Houston. (2 pages)., 1-1-1910 (Box 280, Item 43)
  - Houston city taxes to Texas Town Lot Improvement Company., 12-31-1909. (Box 280, Item 44)
  - Inventory of appraisement of property owned by Texas Town Lot Improvement Company in the city of Houston. (2 pages)., 1-1-1909 (Box 280, Item 45)
  - Inventory of appraisement of property owned by H. B. Masterson., 1-1- 1920. (Box 280, Item 46)
  - Letter from tax collector of La Porte, TX to H. Masterson Texas Town Lot Improvement Company telling of delinquent school taxes., 10-28-1921. (Box 280, Item 47)
  - (6) Receipts to Honora Steel Perry from the Office of the Tax Collector of Harris Co. (7 pages)., 8-8-1912. (Box 280, Item 48)
  - Inventory of appraisement of property owned by Honoro Steel Perry in the city of Houston., 1-1-1912. (Box 280, Item 49)
  - (6) Inventories of property owned by Texas Town Lot Improvement Company., 1921 (Box 280, Item 50)
  - Inventory of appraisement of property owned by Texas Town Lot Improvement Company in the city of Houston. (2 pages)., 1-1-1913 (Box 280, Item 51)
  - Inventory of appraisement of property owned by Mrs. L. Masterson in the city of Houston., 1-11-1911 (Box 280, Item 52)
  - Inventory of appraisement of property owned by Texas Town Lot Improvement Company in the city of Houston. (5 pages)., 1-1-1912 (Box 280, Item 53)
  - Houston City Taxes receipt for Texas Town Lot Improvement Company., 12-31-1912 (Box 280, Item 54)
  - Redemption receipt for taxes paid by H.B Mrs. P.J. Masterson., 12-5-1911. (Box 280, Item 55)
  - Redemption receipt from Angleton Independent School District for taxes paid by the Masterson Irrigation Company., 2-12-1918. (Box 280, Item 56)
  - Certificate of redemption from Brazoria Company to H. Masterson., 9-14-1912. (Box 280, Item 57)
  - Letter from A. E. Masterson (Angleton, TX) to H. Masterson (Houston, TX) concerning redemption covering the Wm. Tennis property at Alvin., 6-15- 1914. (Box 280, Item 58)
  - Inventory of appraisement of property owned by W.A. Smith in the city of Houston. Rendered by T.S. Masterson., 1-1-1909 (Box 280, Item 59)
  - Inventory of appraisement of property owned by T.S. Masterson in the city of Houston., 1-1-1909. (Box 280, Item 60)
  - Inventory of appraisement of property owned by H. Masterson in the city of Houston., 1-1-1909. (Box 280, Item 61)
  - Inventory of appraisement of property owned by A. E. Masterson in the city of Houston., 1-1-1909. (Box 280, Item 62)
  - Inventory of appraisement of property owned by Mrs. LJ. Masterson in the city of Houston., 1-1-1909. (Box 280, Item 63)
  - Inventory of appraisement of property owned by T. S. Masterson in the city of Houston. (2 pages)., 1-1-1909. (Box 280, Item 64)
  - (2) Inventories of appraisement of property owned by W.A. Smith in the city of Houston., 1-1-1911. (Box 280, Item 65)
  - List of real estate in Madina Company rendered to LB. Bostwick, Assessor Collector of Brazoria Co. for assessment of taxes.(fragmented)., 8-18-1869 (Box 280, Item 66)
  - List of real estate situated in Kinney Co. rendered by LB. Bostwick, Assessor Collector of Brazoria Co. for assessment of taxes., 8-15-1869. (Box 280, Item 67)
  - (28) Inventories of appraisement of property owned by Texas Town Lot Improvement Company in the city of Houston. (33 pages)., 1-1-1912. (Box 280, Item 68)
  - (7) Inventories of appraisement of property owned by H. Masterson in the city of Houston., 1-1-1912. (Box 280, Item 69)
  - (2) Inventories of appraisement of property owned by W.A. Smith in the city of Houston. [MISSING], 1-1-1912. (Box 280, Item 70)
  - Inventory of appraisement of property owned by Mrs. LJ. Masterson in the city of Houston., 1-1-1912. (Box 280, Item 71)
  - (5) Inventories of appraisement of property owned by Texas Town Lot Improvement Company in the city of Houston., 1-1-1912. (Box 280, Item 72)
  - Inventory of appraisement of property owned by H. Masterson in the city of Houston., 1-1-1912. (Box 280, Item 73)
  - Inventory of property owned by H. Masterson rendered for assessment of taxes in 1918 by N.T. Masterson (2 pages). (Box 280, Item 74)
  - Inventory of property owned by LJ. Masterson rendered for assessment of taxes in 1918 by N.T. Masterson. (Box 280, Item 75)
  - Inventory of property owned by Masterson Irrigation Co. rendered for assessment of taxes in 1918 by N.T. Masterson. (Box 280, Item 76)
  - (4) Inventories of property owned by Texas Town Lot Improvement Co. rendered for assessment of taxes in 1918 by N.J. Masterson. (Box 280, Item 77)
  - (2) Inventories of property owned by Masterson Irrigation Company rendered for assessment of taxes for 1919. (Box 280, Item 78)
  - Inventory of property owned by H. Masterson Jr. rendered for assessment of taxes for 1919. (Box 280, Item 79)
  - Inventory of property owned by N.J. Masterson rendered for assessment of taxes for 1919. (Box 280, Item 80)
  - (5) Inventories of property owned by Texas Town Lot Improvement Company rendered for assessment of taxes for 1919. (Box 280, Item 81)
  - Inventory of property owned by N.J. Masterson Trustee rendered for assessment of taxes for 1919. (Box 280, Item 82)
  - Inventory of property owned by L.J. Masterson rendered for assessment of taxes for 1919. (Box 280, Item 83)
  - (2) Inventories of property owned by H. Masterson rendered for assessment of taxes for 1919. (Box 280, Item 84)
  - Inventory of property owned by L.J. Masterson rendered for assessment of taxes for 1920. (Box 280, Item 85)
  - Inventory of property owned by H.B. Masterson rendered for assessment of taxes for 1920. (Box 280, Item 86)
  - Inventory of property owned by H. Masterson rendered for assessment of taxes for 1920. (Box 280, Item 87)
  - (4) Inventories of property owned by N.T. Masterson rendered for assessment of taxes for 1920. (Box 280, Item 88)
  - Inventory of property owned by Texas Town Lot Improvement Company rendered for assessment of taxes for 1920. (Box 280, Item 89)
  - (2) Inventories of property owned by Masterson Irrigation Company rendered for assessment of taxes for 1920. (Box 280, Item 90)